威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们现在到了最后一节课和
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We now reach
our final section classes and
原型面向对象编程，但特别关注下
prototypes object oriented programming,
but particularly focusing on under
我们每天在 JavaScript 中看到的一些特性是什么。
the hood, what are some of these features
that we see day to day in JavaScript.
像这样的原型链，我们听说像这样的原型财产，我们看到
Like this prototype chain we hear about
like this prototype property, we see on
我们的函数，就像我们看到的这个新的关键词，就像我们看到的这个类关键词。
our Functions, like this new key word we
see, like this class key word we see.
这些到底是什么意思？
What are of these actually mean?
在这里，我们甚至没有过多地关注于构建 AOP 范例，而是使用
We're not even per se so much focused here
on building out the AOP paradigm as using
作为一个透镜，我们理解它在 JavaScript 中的实现,
that as a lens from which we understand
the implementation of it in JavaScript,
意思是了解原型链。
meaning understand prototype chain.
这真是一件优雅而美丽的东西。
It's a really elegant and beautiful thing.
我又用优雅了，不知道是什么意思。
I'm using elegant again
not know what it means.
这是一个真正的，这是一个东西，我们走吧。
It's a really, it's a thing, there we go.
好了，我们走吧。
All right, there we go.
所以这是一个非常流行的范例，用于构造我们复杂的代码。
So an enormously popular paradigm for
structuring our complex code.
年复一年的面向对象编程
Object oriented programming for
years and years and
我们处理一个文件中10万行代码的方式。
years has been the way that we handle
having 100,000 lines of code in one file.
不是一个文件，一个应用程序，有一些结构这样
Not really one file, one application,
having some structure so
不只是这样，然后这样，然后这样，然后这样
it's not just do this, then this,
then this, then this and
这里，但某种组织结构。
this here, but
some sort of organizing structure.
在 JavaScript 中，它依赖于原型链。
in JavaScript,
it depends on the prototype chain.
这是幕后功能，使我们能够实现一些
This is the behind the scenes feature
that enables us to achieve some
类似于 JavaScript 中的面向对象模式。
semblance of object oriented
pattern in JavaScript.
但是我也要说，一个本身就很有吸引力的工具是非常不错的。
But it's also as I'm saying a compelling
tool in its own right is pretty nice.
我们要理解原型和原型的区别。
We're gonna understand the difference
between proto and prototype.
我们将看到新的类，新的类关键字。
We're going to see the new class,
the new in class keywords.
尽管我们能够真诚地去理解，比如说,
As much honestly for
us to be able to understand, for example,
在采访中，最受欢迎的问题之一是一个中高级开发人员
in interview where one of the most popular
questions to ask of a mid senior developer
引擎盖下的新词是什么。
is, what's the newkey word
doing under the hood.
我们将从头开始构建它，以完全理解它
We're going to build it out from
scratch to fully understand it
让我们的工作自动化，但是
as an allowed to automate
some of our work, but
我们也将看到我们的功能和词汇范围的力量。
we're also going to see the power of our
functions and lexical scoping within them.
我们来看看这个关键词是如何工作的。
We're going to see how this keyword works.
我们还要学习一下这个大的 Headline 对象,
We're going to also learn about
that big Headline object,
原型，我们得到所有的共享函数和所有的对象。
the object.prototype, where we get all
our shared functions and all objects get.
接下来，我们将从提醒自己
All to come, we're gonna start it
off with reminding ourselves what
甚至是开发和运行代码的核心。
even is the core of development and
running code.
我们要记住两件事: 保存数据和运行代码。
Two things we do remember,
save data and run code.
在一个典型的应用程序中，例如,
In a typical application that might be,
for example,
这个测验游戏，保存分数
the quiz games, saving the scores and
两个用户的用户名，也许是100个用户，1000个用户同时在玩。
the user names of two users, maybe 100
users, 1000 users all playing at once.
不要以为在用户界面上看到,
Don't think that by seeing on the UI,
比如看益智游戏的视觉效果，这就是保存的数据。
like looking at the quiz games
visuals that that's the data saved.
这就是显示的数据，它保存在 Java 内存的幕后。
That's the data displayed, it saved
behind the scenes in Java's memory.
它就是这样存在的，所以它不是魔术，它仍然在幕后。
That's how it's there, so it's not magic,
it's still behind the scenes.
这些只是像素。
Those are just pixels.
它是电脑的幕后工作。
It's a behind the scenes of the computer.
另一半运行在应用程序开发或
The other half run over
application development or
运行代码实际上是运行代码，功能函数的数据。
running code is to actually run code,
functionality functions on that data.
例如，我们有一个用户想用它来增加用户得分
For example, we've got a user want to
use it to increasing user to score
当他们答对一道测验题的时候。
when they get a quiz question right.
就是这样。
That is it.
顺便说一句，我不知道为什么我们有10万行代码
By the way, I don't know how we therefore
have a hundred thousand lines of code and
太复杂了，就是这样。
it's so complex, because that's it.
为什么学习如此困难？
Why is learning so hard?
在一个问答游戏中，你知道吗，我需要拯救很多用户。
In a quiz game, you know what,
I need to save a lot of users.
但不仅仅是用户，我还要保存,
But not just even users,
I've got to save and by the way,
它们都有很多不同的属性，关于它们的信息。
all of them have lots of different
properties, information about them.
分数，用户名，头像，个人资料网址，电子邮件商店,
Score, username, avatar,
profile URL, email store,
状态，他们与应用程序接触的最后状态。
status, last status of their
engagement with the application.
这仅仅是个开始，仅仅是用法。
And that's just the start,
that's just usage.
人们有管理员，我们有测验问题需要保存。
People's got admins,
we've got quiz questions we need to save.
我们得到了测验的结果。
We've got quiz outcomes.
我们有排名表和其他1000件作品。
We've got league tables and
1000 other pieces.
所有这些都有数据存储在我们的应用程序运行时的内存和
All of these have data stored in our
applications runtime in the memory and
关联的功能，这是代码，我们可以用来交互和
associated functionality that is code
that we can use to interact with and
利用这些数据。
use that data.
或者显示它，呈现它，显示它，更改它更新,
Or display it, render it,
display it, change it alter updated,
删除它为所有的应用程序是功能和
delete it whatever for
all application is functionality and
运行相关数据。
the associated data to run on that.
所以如果我们从用户开始，我不知道，这可能会增加分数。
So if we start with users, it might be,
I don't know, increasing that score.
它可以显示这些但在100,000行代码,
It could be displaying these but
in 100,000 lines of code,
很快就会变得很复杂。
it gets really complicated really fast.
当我需要它时，它的功能在哪里？
Where is the functionality when I need it?
我有我的用户1，我有他们的得分和名字的可爱数据,
I've got my user one and I've got the
lovely data of their score and their name,
他们的用户名，但我想更新分数。
their username, but
I want to update the score.
但是让我给分数打分的功能在哪里呢？
But where's the function that
allows me to rate the score?
我有100,000行代码，函数在哪里？
I've got 100,000 lines of code,
where is that function?
不仅如此，这个函数只适用于用户评分。
Not only that, that function
only applies to the users score.
不要让我试图开始，我不知道，或者我认为这是一种改变
Don't get me trying to start, I don't
know, or I suppose it was like a change
用户名，或者，更新用户图像。
username, or yeah, update users image.
不要试图在我的排行榜上使用这个功能。
Don't try and use that
functionality on my league tables.
不要试图在我的测验问题上使用这个功能。
Don't try to use that
functionality on my quiz question.
所以我不仅不知道功能在我的百里哪里
So not only I do not know where
the functionality is in my hundred
上千行代码。
thousand lines of code.
我不知道它适用于我的哪一部分数据
I don't know which bits of
my data it applies to and
这就是为什么编码如此复杂。
that's what makes coding so complex.
这么多的数据，这么多的功能，它只适用于某些位。
So much data, so much functionality and
it only applies to certain bits.
找到正确的功能
And finding the right functionality and
确保它只适用于正确的位,
making sure it only
applies to the right bit,
我们需要某种组织结构。
we need some sort of organizing structure.
我称之为这里的一小部分，很容易理解。
I call that the bit here,
easy to reason about.
我希望我的代码很容易理解发生了什么。
I want my code to be easy to
figure out what's going on.
但我也希望我的代码易于添加特性。
But I also want my code to
be easy to add features to.
这对于任何给定的数据都是新的功能，就像用户得到的那样
That is new functionality for
any given data, like users got
他们现在可以，我不知道，他们现在可以登录 Facebook。
new functionality they can now, I don't
know, they can now log in with Facebook.
我想很容易地添加功能。
I want to be easy to add functionality.
但我不希望所有这些都以牺牲为代价
But I don't want all of
that to come at the expense
我的代码是合理的性能低效率，因为它可能会这样做。
of my code being reasonably performance
unefficient cuz it might well do so.
面向对象的范例，以及
The object oriented paradigm, and
实际上所有的代码范例都是指导方针的集合,
really all paradigms of code,
they're sets of guidelines,
它们是让我们实现这三个目标的最佳实践方法。
they're best practices approaches that
allow us to achieve these three things.
它们是组织我们代码的一系列方式，它们将一起工作
They are kind of a bunch of ways of
organizing our code that will together
希望能达到这三个目标。
hopefully achieve these three goals.
这就是我们要做的，我们要实现这三个目标,
And that's what it's about,
we're gonna achieve all three of these,
顺便说一句，我认为。
by the way from solution
to on was in my opinion.
但是由于开发者通常来自其他语言,
But because developers often
come from other languages,
他们认为什么是容易推理的，可能不是
their idea of what easy to
reason about might not be
编写和组织我们的代码的 JavaScript 本地风格。
a JavaScript native style of writing and
organizing our code.
所以解决方案三和四实现结构化我们的代码在一个可管理的方式,
So solution three and four for achieving
structuring our code in a manageable way,
主要是关于写作方面的人手不足
are primarily going to be
about shorthands for writing
让它看起来更像其他编程语言的代码。
the code that make it look a little bit
more like other programming languages.
换句话说，更容易推理但是
In other words easier to reason about but
真的很容易推理，只要你明白这一点。
really easy to reason about,
only if you understand it under the hood.